她是洛 简简单单穿着袜子的洛在清晨
She was Lo. Plain Lo in the morning.
身高四尺十寸
Standing four feet ten in one sock.
穿着松裤的时候是洛拉
She was Lola in slacks.
在学校的时候她是多丽
She was Dolly at school.
她书面上的名字是多丽丝
She was Dolores on the dotted line.
在我怀里 她永远是
In my arms, she was always...
洛丽塔
..Lolita.
我的生命之光
Light of my life.
欲望之火
Fire of my loins.
我的罪恶
My sin.
我的灵魂
My soul.
洛丽塔
Lolita.
但是如果没有在我在安娜贝尔第一次遇见她
But there might have been\nno Lolita at all...
也就不会有洛丽塔
..had I not first met Annabel.
当时我们都只有14岁
We were both 14.
在一个男孩的14岁的夏天时 不管什么事发生
Whatever happens to a boy\nduring the summer he's 14...
都可以让他铭记一生
..can mark him for life.
你所看到的宾馆 米兰那
That hotel you see, the Mirana,...
属于我们
..that belonged to us.
她那时想当一名护士
She wanted to be a nurse.
我想当一名间谍
I wanted to be a spy.
最终我们疯狂地 无可救药地相爱
All at once we were madly,\nhopelessly in love.
四个月之后 她死于伤寒
Four months later, she died of typhus.
她的去世所带来的巨大的打击冻结了我的情感
The shock other death\nfroze something in me.
我所爱的那个孩子已经去了
The child I loved was gone.
但是我一直在寻找她
But I kept looking for her...
很久以后我抛弃了我的童年
..long after I'd left\nmy own childhood behind.
就如同毒药渗入伤口
The poison was in the wound, you see.
伤口永远不能治愈
And the wound wouldn't heal.
或许我应该加入教士
I probably should have\njoined the priesthood.
与其相反 我接受了美国比尔兹利大学的教职
Instead, I accepted a teaching post\nat Beardsley College in America.
在秋季开学之前我有一个夏天的假期
I had a summer free\nbefore the Fall semester.
我想我应该完成我正在写的一本书
I thought I'd finish\na textbook I was working on.
一个法国文化对美国学生影响的调查
A survey of French literature\nfor American students.
我接受了预付款
I took my advance...\nI took my advance...
准备去我叔叔的一个名字叫莫克的朋友家居住
..and went to live at the house of friends\nof my late uncle's, the McCoos,...
他家在拉姆斯戴尔的新英格兰镇
..in the New England town of Ramsdale.
但是当我到达后 我发现那个房子已经不在那里了
But on arriving, I found\nthat it was no longer there.
但是莫克夫人的一个朋友
But a friend of Mrs McCoo,...
一个名叫夏洛特·海兹的寡妇
..a widow, Mrs Charlotte Haze,...
同意向我提供住处
..agreed to accommodate me.
该死的狗！
-Goddamn dog!
等一会 我正在煮东西
One minute. Something's burnin'.
老天爷慈悲为怀
Lord have mercy!
海兹夫人很快就下来
Mrs Haze'll be down in one.
露易丝 是汉伯特教授吗？\n告诉他我很快下来
Is that Professor Humbert,\nLouise? Tell him I'll be down in one.
她很快就下来
She'll be down in one!
汉伯特先生
Monsieur Humbert.
啊 我是
Uh, yes.
你是海兹太太？
Mrs Haze, is it?
叫我夏洛特
Charlotte.
非常高兴认识你
I am so pleased\nto make your acquaintance.
弗兰克 莫克告诉了我你所有的学者气质的爱好
Frank McCoo told me all about\nyour scholarly pursuits.
我自己也非常喜欢法语
I myself just cherish the French tongue.
嗯 麻烦 我能不能
Um... I wonder, could l...
嗯 请进
Mm. Come in.
哈罗德和我 已故的海兹先生
Harold and l, the late Mr Haze,...
我们都比较喜欢墨西哥
..we simply adored Mexico.
觉得他们的文化是那么的古老
The whole idea\nof a culture that sophisticated.
另外我们也认为他们跟原始人一样
And we think of them as primitive.
我是说 看看我们
I mean, look at us!
没错 是的
Indeed, yes.
楼上
Upstairs.
我和洛的房间在这边
I and Lo have our rooms just there.
这是你的房间
And this is your room.
可以放下一张桌子 随便你放什么东西
Space for a desk, anything you want.
20美元一个月 不还价
And at $20 a month,\nyou can't beat the price.
这是卫生间 有点乱
And here's the bathroom.\nIt's a bit of a mess.
这是厨房
And this is the kitchen.
如果你有什么特殊的东西想吃的就直说
Now, if you have any special\nfood needs, you just say.
我不知道拉姆斯戴尔有没有鹅肝 就跟你平常习惯吃的那样
I don't know if Ramsdale can provide you\nwith foie grass, like you're used to.
那是什么？
What's that?
嗯 时间表 当我....
Uh... timetable. For when I um...
真希望我不必回去 但是我想我必须回到纽约去
I was hoping I wouldn't have to,\nbut I think I've got to go back to New York.
-噢 看来你不是很满意\n-不是 有一个关于波德莱尔的会议要参加
-Oh, you're not too favourably impressed.\n-No... There's a Baudelaire conference...
或许房子收拾得不是很整洁 \n但是你住在这里会很舒适
This is not a neat household,\nbut you would be very comfortable here.
确实很舒适
Very comfortable indeed.
我带你看看后院你就不会说不了
Don't say no until you've seen the piazza.
来吧
Come.
我把这个地方叫后院
Well, I call it the piazza.
保持这里健康绿色可花了我不少功夫
It's so much work\nto keep it healthy and green.
一辈子的工作
It's a life's work.
那就是我的洛
That's my Lo.
这是我的百合花
And these are my lilies.
我喜欢百合
I love lilies.
-Lily 是个漂亮的名字 你说呢？\n-非常漂亮
-Lily's a nice name, don't you think?\n-Beautiful.
漂亮
Beautiful!
你刚才说房费是多少来着？
How much did you say the room was?
如果给一个普通男人
A normal man,...
一些女学生的照片
..given a group photograph\nof schoolgirls...
并被要求选出最喜欢的那一个
..and asked to point out\nthe loveliest one,...
他必定不会选择那个早熟的
..will not necessarily choose\nthe nymphet among them.
你必须是个艺术家
You have to be an artist,...
一个疯子 充满廉耻感并且忧郁而且绝望的人
..a madman, full of shame\nand melancholy and despair,...
才能认出她们之中的那个致命的恶魔
..in order to recognize\nthe little deadly demon among the others.
她站在那里
She stands...
没有被认出来
..unrecognized by them,...
对她自己的神奇的魔力一无所知
..unconscious herself\nof her fantastic power.
-待会见 短吻鳄\n-待会见 鳄鱼
-See you later, alligator.\n-After a while, crocodile!
-很快 丹尼尔布恩\n-去死 蠢鸭子
-Real soon, Daniel Boone.\n-Get fucked, Daffy Duck.
♪ 不知道为什么\n天上看不到太阳 ♪
♪ Don't know why...\nthere's no sun up in the sky ♪
♪ 自从我的爱人和我不在一起 ♪
♪ Stormy weather ♪
♪ 天气一直是暴风雨 ♪
♪ Since my man and I ain't together... ♪
你把我吵醒了
You woke me up.
-对不起
-Sorry.
我停下来
I'll stop.
多丽丝！\n你整理了你的床铺了吗？
Dolores!\nHave you made your bed?
没有 我没有整理我的床铺
No, I have not made my bed.
我让你整理你的床铺 有没有？
I asked you to make your bed, didn't l?
没有 你问我有没有整理我的床铺
No. You asked me if I'd made my bed.
整理你的床铺
Make your bed.
-现在!
-Now!
我期待一个可怕的灾难
I long for some terrific disaster.
地震
Earthquake.
壮观的爆炸
Spectacular explosion.
整理你的床铺！
Make your bed!
她妈立即终结了它
Her mother instantly eliminated.
用能让方圆一公里的人能听到的声音
Along with everybody else\nfor miles around.
洛丽塔
Lolita...
在我怀里
..in my arms.
我今天很困
I'm sleepy today.
我也是
Me too.
你有失眠过吗？
Have you been having trouble sleeping?
你不能想象那有多痛苦
You can't imagine.
我是不是有丘疹？
Am I getting a zit?
什么？
What?
你看见我下巴上的疙瘩了吗？
Do you see a pimple on my chin?
在我看来 你绝对完美
You look absolutely perfect to me.
想看看我下巴颤动吗？
Wanna see my chin wobble?
好
OK.
汉伯特
Humbert!
Humbert...
她有没有一直烦你？
Is she keeping you up?
不好意思？
I beg your pardon?
没有！
No!
没有 没有 我
No. No, I'm...
没有
No.
大概是一个24小时漏洞
Well, it's probably just a 24-hour bug.
他想见你
He was looking forward to meeting you.
有人看见我的另一只球鞋吗？
Has anybody seen my other sneaker?!
你的早餐 汉伯特教授
Your breakfast, Professor Humbert.
别告诉我妈 我吃完了你的熏肉
Don't tell Mother, but I ate all your bacon.
-多丽丝 刚才是法洛夫人\n-那又怎样？
-Dolores, that was Mrs Farlow.\n-So?
露丝发烧不能去Hourglass湖了
Rose has a temperature\nand can't go to Hourglass Lake.
-哦 然后？\n-别用那种口气跟我说话！
-Oh, yeah?\n-Do not use that tone with me!
你准备好去教堂了吗？
Are you ready for church?
我才不去那个恶心的教堂
I'm not going to that disgusting church.
-年轻人\n-不去野餐我就不去教堂
-Young lady...\n-No picnic, no church.
好吧真没良心
That is fine with me.\nIt is your conscience.
我回来的时候你的房间要整整齐齐
I want your room spick-and-span\nwhen I get home.
-另外洗你的头发\n-我洗过了
-And wash your hair, young lady.\n-I did wash it!
-什么时候？\n-几个月前
-When?\n-A couple of months ago.
我可以称为一个舞蹈家
I could be a dancer.
那是我主要的选择
That's a major option.
因为我有与生俱来的优雅
Cos I do have a natural grace.
-你知道 一种悲伤的美丽\n-一种悲伤倒没错
-You know. A kind of sad beauty.\n-Sort of sad is right.
我有空想看看你跳舞
I'd like to see you dance sometime.
小女孩总想称为芭蕾舞演员 不是吗？
Little girls always want to be\nballerinas, don't they?
我想我是
I know I did.\nI know I did.
但是我曾经是 怎么说呢？\n太 丰满了？
But I was -how should I put it? -\na tad too... plump?
-这个词有没有错？\n-没错
-Is that the right word?\n-Yes.
我再去倒点酒
I'll get more Vouvray.
让她明天带我们去hourglass 湖
Make her take us\nto Hourglass Lake tomorrow.
-我？\n-嗯
-Me?\n-Mm-hm.
你说什么她都会答应
She'll do anything you say.
她对你着迷了
She's getting a thing about you.
小点声 小点声
Whisper, whisper.
你们两个在咕叽什么？
What are you two so cozy about?
嗯 我有没有告诉过你们
Um... Did I ever tell you both that...
我曾经是
..I was once a...
..that I was once a... um...
嗯 我\n我曾经在北极当过厨子？
Uh... that l...\nI was once a cook in the North Pole?
-厨子？\n-嗯 也不完全是
-A cook?\n-Well, not exactly a cook.
我开过几个罐头
I opened a few cans.
是个气候考察\n我曾经打过北极熊
It was a weather expedition.\nAnd I shot a polar bear.
-不会吧\n-好吧 我没打中
-No!\n-Well, I didn't hit it.
为什么开枪打北极熊？\n这事可真恶心
Why shoot a polar bear?\nThat's a lousy thing to do.
因为我发现
Because I found it...
用它的脸 听着-\n在冰激凌机里面
..with its face -Listen to this -\nin the ice-cream mixer.
这段我没法忘记\n因为我们靠冰激凌机过活
I couldn't let that pass\nbecause we lived off ice cream.
你已经语无伦次了 汉伯特
You're out of your gourd, Humpy.
你能不能不要用这个布娃娃来烦人了？
Will you stop fidgeting with the doll?
现在我们都认为洛应该去睡觉了
And now we all think\nthat Lo should go to bed.
洛？
Lo?
你的“我们”是指谁 白脸女人？
What do you mean "we", paleface?
如我所说 我把我的打北极熊的枪
So, as I was saying, there I was\nwith my white polar-bear gun...
来搅拌
-..to blend in.
找我的！
It's for me!
喂？
Hello?
-不 不好意思 她很忙\n-希望你原谅她的没礼貌
-No, I'm sorry. She's busy.\n-I hope you will forgive her bad manners.
-又怎么样？！
-Now what?!
看着 我的独创现代舞
Look! It's my modern dance creation!
多丽丝·海兹 关掉那音乐！
Dolores Haze, turn that music down!
她是个害虫 如果她打扰了你的思考的话直接抽她就行
She is a pest. Just slap her hard\nif she interferes with your meditations.
切！
Psst!
嗯
Hum...
汉 你是不是认为我有一个很野心的梦？
Hum, do you know that I have\none most ambitious dream?
去找一个真正培训过的女仆人
To get a hold of a real trained maid...
就跟那个德国女孩子一样\n跟那个塔波特说的一样
..like that German girl\nthat the Talbots spoke of...
让她住在房子里面
..and have her live in the house.
-没房间了吧\n-噢 亲爱的 亲爱的
-No room.\n-Oh, chéri, chéri.
你低估了我们的那卑微的房子
You underestimate the possibilities\nof our humble household.
我会让她住在洛的房间里
We'd put her in Lo's room.
我本来打算把门开在客人房的
I intended to turn that hole\ninto a guest room anyway.
那么洛睡在哪里？
But where would Lo sleep?
小洛完全不在此计划中
Little Lo does not enter the picture at all.
小洛将会去参加寄宿学校举行的野营活动
Little Lo goes straight from camp\nto a good boarding school...
有严格的纪律\n以及一些合理的宗教培训
..with strict discipline\nand some sound religious training.
我不去！
I won't go!
我要把所有这些名字标签在明天都缝到你的衣服上
I want all of these name tags\nsewn on your clothes by tomorrow.
我不想去
I don't want to go.
我想我不是在征求你的意见
I didn't ask your opinion!
我不想去你不能强迫我
I don't want to go and you can't make me.
听着 我们都认为这是个好主意
Look, we all think it's a good idea.
汉伯特教授认为这是个好主意\n我认为这是个好主意 你必须得去
Professor Humbert thinks it's a good idea,\nI think it's a good idea, and you are going!
两面派！
Double-crosser!
嗷
Ow!
我一个小时之前就让你把箱子塞进车子里了
I asked you to put that suitcase\nin the car an hour ago!
露易丝 非常感谢你帮助这屁孩子
Louise, thank you so much\nfor helping the poor child.
天杀的！多丽丝 我告诉你把野餐篮子放在后座上！
Goddamn it! Dolores, I told you\nto put this lunch basket in the back seat!
为什么老是让我去做什么？
Why always tell me to do everything?
我是唯一的不吃你那一套的
I'm the one that won't be eating it.
露易丝！晚饭吃布鲁塞尔菜芽和面包夹肉
Louise! Brussels sprouts\nand meat loaf for dinner.
-好的 开车小心\n-谢谢 走了
-All right. Drive careful.\n-Thank you. Let's go!
-再见 夫人\n-再见 露易丝
-Bye, my baby.\n-Bye, Louise.
-你真是太好了 我会想你的\n-啊！
-You be good. I'm gonna miss you.\n-Agh!
多丽丝！
Dolores!
快走！
Let's go!
快点！
Speed it up!
快上车！
Get in the car!
又要干吗？这屁孩子！
Now what?! That child!
-露易丝 牛腰肉也行\n-好的
-Louise, maybe tenderloin.\n-That'd be good.
我在等着！
I'm waiting!
有没有跟你说过 \n我已经跟你说过一千次了
If I've told you once,\nI've told you a thousand times...
别让我在车上等你
..not to make me wait in the car.
如果你不是去野营 \n我就把你给撂倒
If you weren't going to camp,\nI would ground you.
汉伯先生！
Mr Humble!
这些该死的楼梯快把我给整死了
These damn stairs\nare gonna be the death of me.
汉伯先生！
Mr Humble!
汉伯先生？
Mr Humble?
我有东西要给你
I have something for you.
哦 是吧
Oh, yes.
我要走了 很快就回来
I'm leaving, but I'll be back later.
你他娘的还在那里干什么？
What the hell he doin' in there?
这是一个忏悔
This is a confession.
我爱你
I love you.
我是个激情的可爱的女人？
I'm a passionate and lonely woman...
你是我一生所爱
..and you are the love of my life.
现在你知道了
Now you know.
请毁了这封信然后走吧
So please, destroy this letter and go.
我将会在晚餐时回来\n你那时必须走
I shall return by dinner time\nand you must be gone by then.
听着 亲爱的 如果我发现你在家？
You see, chéri, if I found you at home,...
如果你仍然在家那么只代表一件事
..the fact of your remaining\nwould mean only one thing.
你需要我就跟我需要你一样 \n称为一生的伴侣
That you want me as much as I do you,\nas a lifelong mate,...
而且你已经准备将你\n和我的生命永远连在一起
..and that you are ready to link up\nyour life with mine forever and ever...
并且做我女儿的父亲
..and be a father to my little girl.
两周之后 \n我们在一个简单的仪式中结了婚
Two weeks later,\nwe were married in a simple ceremony.
老海兹确保小海兹没有参加
Big Haze made sure little Haze\nwas not in attendance.
嗯 这可真是天降的福气
Mm. This is bliss.
这简直是地上的天堂 不是吗 汉？
This is heaven on earth. Isn't it, Hump?
嗯
Mm.
你在写你的书吗？
Are you working on your book?
是的
Yes.
哦 一个秘密的抽屉 里面是什么？
Oh, a secret drawer. What's in there?
锁起来的情书
Locked-up love letters.
钥匙在哪里？
Where's the key?
藏起来了
Hidden.
"I'm in the Mood for Love"
"I'm in the Mood for Love")
在我们结婚后的头六周
During the six weeks\nwe'd been married,...
我成功地逃脱了大部分的丈夫的职责
..I successfully avoided\nmost of my husbandly duties.
整个七月 我一直给夏洛特各种不同的安眠药 ?
Throughout July, I'd been offering\nCharlotte various sleeping tablets,...
她很开心地吞下它们
..which she gobbled down happily.
她吃药很强
She was a great taker of pills.
♪ I'm in the mood for love ♪
♪ Simply because you're near me ♪
♪ Funny, but when you're near me ♪
♪ I'm in the mood for love ♪
♪ Heaven is in your eyes ♪
♪ Bright as the stars we're under ♪
♪ Oh, is it any wonder... ♪
我尝试的最后一种药把她放倒了四个小时
The last dose I had tried\nhad knocked her out for four hours.
但是并不足够能保证我晚上不被打扰
But that was not enough\nto guarantee me an undisturbed night.
汉
Hum...
你逃不出我的手掌心！
At last!
嗯
Mm.
我想这个东西不太管用
I think I must be immune.
嗯…你会给我什么东西 如果你是想
Wh... What would you give me\nif you wanted to uh...
放倒
..to knock out...
比如一头母牛？
..say, a cow?
七八个小时就可以
J-Just for... seven or eight hours.
确保
So that...
这头母牛睡得很死？
..you know, the cow... would stay asleep?
即使你在旁边乱动并转身？
Even if you were\ntossing and turning next to it.
那么
Well...
你为什么不…
Why don't you...
试试这个？
..try these?
最新的药
They're new.
我老婆吃了这药
My wife takes them and...
我整夜都没听到她吭一声
..I don't hear a peep out of her\nall night long.
听起来就是我想要的东西
Sounds like just the thing.
我回家了！
I'm home!
有人吗？
Hello?
海兹老女人？
"The Haze woman."
肥母牛？
"The fat cow"?
讨人厌的大咪咪？
"The obnoxious mamma"?
那么 这个又老又蠢的海兹老女人不会再受你的骗了
Well, the "old stupid Haze woman"\nis no longer your dupe.
夏洛特
Charlotte!
你是个怪物
You're a monster.
-你是个卑鄙的 罪恶的禽兽
-You're a despicable, criminal monster.
-听我说\n-如果你靠近我我会尖叫！
-Now...\n-If you come near me I'll scream!
-听我解释\n-离我远点！
-Let me just...\n-Get away from me!
我今晚就走
I'm leaving tonight.
你可以得到这个房子 我不在乎
You can keep this house. I don't care.
但是你永远不会再看到那个可怜的毛孩子
But you will never see\nthat miserable brat ever again.
现在快滚出我的视线！
Now get out of my sight!
夏洛特 你不能…
Charlotte, you mustn't...
你不能就这样毁了我们的生活
You mustn't ruin our lives.
那只是…
That's...
那只是 那只是我所写的小说的
That's just... That's just a fragment of...
一个片段
..a novel I'm writing.
我只是用了你的名字
I used your name on those...
仅仅图方便
..just for... convenience.
我去弄点喝的
I'll get us a drink.
一点带冰的饮料能让我们头脑清醒
A nice stiff drink\nwill clear both our heads.
夏洛特 我给我们做了点加冰的饮料
Charlotte, I made us a nice stiff drink!
喂？
Yes?
但那真是荒谬
But that's ridiculous.
电话里那个男人说你死了 夏洛特
There's this man on the phone\nsaying you've been killed, Charlotte.
夏洛特？
Charlotte?
对不起
I'm... I'm sorry.
请往后站
Stand back, please.
我妻子在哪里？
Where's my wife?
-你是汉伯特先生吗？\n-我是
-Are you Mr Humbert?\n-I am.
她直接跑向我
She ran right in front of me.
我 我甚至没有看到她
I... I didn't even see her.
先生？
Sir?
对不起 先生
I'm sorry, sir.
这是汉伯特夫人吗？
Is this Mrs Humbert?
先生
Sir,...\nSir,...
这是汉伯特夫人吗？
..is this Mrs Humbert?
噢 老天爷
Oh, God...
噢 老天爷 噢 老天爷！
Oh, God... Oh, God!
她那时正走向邮箱
She was walking to the mailbox.
她准备寄掉这些信
She was going to mail these letters.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
我要回去 躺一会 警官
I'll go and... Lie down, officer.
-可以吗？\n-你直接走吧 先生
-Will that be all right?\n-You go right ahead, sir.
我只是进房间 如果你
I'll just be across in the house if you...
请问这是Enchanted Hunter宾馆吗？
Is that the Enchanted Hunters Hotel?
是的 这是汉伯特先生
Yes. This is Mr Humbert.
明天晚上
Tomorrow night.
只一夜
Just the one night, please.
是的 一个两张床的标准间
Yes, a room with twin beds.
两个人 实际上是一个半人
For two.\nWell, one and a half people, really.
仅仅是我和我的
It's just for me and my...
我的个子不高的 我的小女儿
..my short... my small daughter.
她随时都可能到
She should be here any minute.
我让查理去谷仓那边找她了
I sent Charlie for her over at the barn.
-谁是查理？\n-快点 快点
-Who's Charlie?\n-Come on, come on.
看着我们的这些孩子们交朋友真让人开心
It's such a pleasure to watch\nour young people make friends.
-嗯 谁是查理？\n-她来了
-So uh... who is this Charlie?\n-Here she is.
嗨 老爹
Hi, Dad!
♪ Hum and Mum, Mum and Hum ♪
♪ Hum and Mum, Mum and Hum... ♪
-妈妈怎么样了？\n-嗯 医生说还不确定
-How's Mum?\n-Well... The doctors aren't quite sure.
腹部有问题
It's something abdominal.
讨人厌？
Abominable?
腹部问题
Abdominal.
她在列平威尔的一家特殊的医院里
She's in a special hospital\nover in Lepingville.
所以 我想我们应该 我们应该
So... I thought we'd... we'd...
去布来士兰
..go over to Briceland,...
待一夜然后去那个医院
..spend the night there and...\nvisit the hospital tomorrow.
或者过一天去
Or the next day.
野营玩得开心吗？
So, did you have a good time at camp?
嗯 嗯
Mm-hm.
你知道吗？我想你
You know, I missed you.
我很想你
I missed you a lot.
可我不想你
Well, I didn't miss you.
实际上 我令人作呕地欺骗了你
In fact, I've been\nrevoltingly unfaithful to you.
但又怎样呢？反正你根本一点点都不在乎我
But so what? Cos you don't care\nabout me any more anyway.
为什么你认为我不在乎你？
Why do you think I don't care about you?
你还没有亲我呢？不是吗？
Well, you haven't\nkissed me yet, have you?
噢！
Oh!
-嗯 不好意思 警官\n-有没有看见一辆蓝色的汽车 跟你的差不多？
-Uh, I'm sorry, officer.\n-See a blue sedan, same make as yours?
-他们或许在那个路口超过去了\n-蓝色轿车？没有 我想没有
-They might have passed you at the turn.\n-Blue sedan? No, I don't think... agh!
-我们没有看见蓝色轿车\n-没有 我认为没有
-We didn't see a blue sedan.\n-No, I don't think we did.
你确定是蓝色的？\n我看见一个更像是紫色的
Are you sure it was blue?\nI saw one that was more purple.
或者更像红色
Or maybe it was more red.
好的 谢谢
All right, OK. Thank you.
谢谢
-Thank you!
不要开枪 不要开枪
Don't shoot, don't shoot!
哇！看起来真不错！
Wow! Looks swank!
♪ No, I will never tell lies ♪
♪ But still I'm called Buttercup... ♪
晚上好 我以汉伯特的名字预定了一个房间
Good evening. I have a reservation\nin the name of Humbert.
两张房的标间
Twin-bedded room.
昨晚打过电话的
I called last night.
-两个人\n-哦！
-Two people.\n-Oh!
对不起 汉八哥先生
I'm sorry, Mr Humbug.
这个房间我给你留到了六点半 但是后来没接到你的电话
I held the room with the twin beds for you\ntill 6.30, but I didn't hear from you.
我们保留到了六点半 有花园景色以及基督公约
We hold till 6.30. And with the flower\nshow and Glory of Christ convention...
我名字不是汉八哥 是赫伯特
My name is not Humbug. It's Herbert.
汉伯特
Humbert.
那么随便找个房间吧 找个吊床给我的女儿 她很累了
Just put us in any room. Put a cot in\nfor my daughter. She's very tired.
或许 我可以让你住342房间 有两张床
Perhaps I could put you in room 342.\nIt has a double bed.
我希望可以\n我妻子可能待会就到
I expect we'll manage.\nMy wife may be turning up later.
请在这里签名 先生
Please sign here, mister.
是只漂亮的狗 对吗？
It's a nice dog, huh?
我喜欢狗
I love dogs.
这是我的狗
Well, that's my dog.
它喜欢你
He likes you.
它不是喜欢每个人的
Doesn't like everybody.
它喜欢什么样的？
Who does he like?
他能闻出来甜美的人
He can smell when people are sweet.
他喜欢甜美的人
He likes sweet people.
年轻的漂亮的人
Nice young people.
比如你
Like you.
到了
Here we are.
谢谢
Thanks very much.
等一下 你意思是我们睡在一个房间里？
Wait a sec. You mean\nwe're sleeping in one room?
一张床上？
With one bed?
我让他们送一张吊床过来
I've asked them to send up a cot,...
给我用 如果你愿意的话
..which I'll use, if you like.
你简直是疯了
You're crazy.
为什么 亲爱的？
Why, my darling?
因为 亲爱的
Because, my darling,...
当我亲爱的妈妈发现了 她会和你离婚而且勒死我
..when my darling mother finds out,\nshe'll divorce you and strangle me.
洛
Lo,...
听着
..listen to me a moment.
从一切实际的意图来说 我是你老爹
For all practical purposes,\nI am your father,...
并对你的幸福负责
..and I'm responsible for your welfare.
现在 我们并不富有
Now, we're not rich.
所以 我们旅行的时候我们肯定会\n我的意思是 呆在一起
So when we travel, we-we're sure to be...\nI mean, we'll be thrown together.
有时
Sometimes.
两个人呆在一个宾馆房间里
Two people sharing\nthe same hotel room...
应该 成为一个
..are bound to... enter into a...
我该怎么说？成为
How can I put it? Into a kind of um...
那个词是“乱伦”
The word is "incest".
我感到我们成年了
I feel like we're grown-ups.
我也是
Me too.
我们将会去我们想去的任何地方 对吗？
We get to do whatever we want, right?
想去的任何地方
Whatever we want.
那么好吧
Well, now.
谁叫的派？
Who had the pie?
我
Me.
你在想什么？这是我的吗？
Whaddaya think? Are they me?
-别看\n-为什么？
-Don't look now.\n-Why?
那个坐在角落的家伙
The guy over in the corner.
别看！ 他正盯着我们
Don't look! He was staring at us.
你不觉得那个家伙看起来像奎尔第吗？
Don't you think that guy\nlooks exactly like Quilty?
什么 那个牙医？
What, the dentist?
当然不是 他兄弟
Of course not. His brother.
作家奎尔第\n他是剧作家
The writer Quilty.\nYou know, he writes the plays.
那个抽烟的家伙 他在广告中抽Dromes的烟
The smoking guy.\nHe smokes the Dromes in the ad.
我们在大厅看到过他和他的狗
We saw him in the lobby with his dog.
如果我告诉你我在野营的时候多么不齿
If I tell you how naughty I was at camp,...
你保证不会疯掉？
..you promise you won't be mad?
待会告诉我
Tell me later.
我让你上床睡觉
I want you to go to bed.
你脱衣服的时候我会去楼下
I'll go downstairs while you...
当我回来时 我希望你已经睡着
When I come up, I want you to be asleep.
好吗？
All right?
我真是个恶心的女孩子
I've been such a disgusting girl.
让我告诉你吧
Just let me tell you.
明天再说
Tell me tomorrow.
我现在就走 明白？
I'm going to go now. All right?
晚安 老爹
Good night, Dad.
晚安
Night-night.
陪审团的女士们
Gentlewomen of the jury,...
如果我的快乐可以言表
..if my happiness could have talked,...
那么那个宾馆将会充满震耳欲聋的呐喊
..it would have filled that hotel\nwith a deafening roar.
我只是后悔
My only regret...
没有立即把342房间的钥匙保存在办公室里
..is that I did not immediately deposit\nkey number 342 at the office...
然后离开那个小镇 那个国家 那个星球 就在那天晚上
..and leave the town, the country,\nthe planet, that very night.
上帝知道一切 上帝看到一切 上帝宽恕一切
The Lord knows all,\nthe Lord sees all, the Lord forgives all.
你在哪里得到的这个魔女？
Where the devil did you get her?
-不好意思？\n-我说马上就会下雨
-I beg your pardon?\n-I said the weather's getting better.
看起来是的
It seems so.
这个女孩子是谁？
Who's the lassie?
嗯
Um...
这是我女儿
It's my daughter.
你撒谎 她不是
You lie. She's not.
什么？
What?
我说七月份很热 （谐音）
I said July was hot.
她妈妈在哪里？
Where's her mother?
去世了
Dead.
噢 抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
你们明天中午和我共进午餐怎么样？
Why don't you two\nlunch with me tomorrow?
那群牧师很快就要走了
That clerical crowd will be gone soon.
嗯
Um...
我们也很快就走的 谢谢
We'll be gone too, thanks.
晚安
Good night.
抱歉 我喝醉了 晚安
Sorry. I'm very drunk. Good night.
你孩子需要好好睡一觉
That child of yours needs a lot of sleep.
波斯人说“睡眠是一朵玫瑰”
"Sleep is a rose" the Persians say.
抽烟吗？
Smoke?
现在不抽 谢谢
Not just now, thanks.
晚安
Good night.
好好享受
Enjoy.
和查理一起回船上来 你们不必这样
Get back in the boat with Charlie.\nYou don't have to do that.
回船上来
Back in the boat.
我渴了
I'm thirsty.
我给你倒点东西喝
I'll bring you something.
你 你和查理玩那个了？野营的时候？
You... You played that with Charlie?\nAt camp?
别告诉你小时侯从来没有尝试过
Don't tell me you never tried it\nwhen you were a kid.
从来没有
Never.
我想我应该给你看一切
I guess I'm gonna have to\nshow you everything.
陪审团的女士们
Gentlewomen of the jury,...
我甚至不是她的第一个爱人
..I was not even her first lover.
你在看什么？
What are you reading?
没什么
Nothing.
什么事？
What's the matter?
没什么
Nothing.
洛
Lo...
你知道你的那个朋友\n-查理-野营的那个
You know that friend of yours\n-Charlie -at camp?
他是第一个？
Was he the first one?
我们能不能不要谈这个？
Can we please get off the subject?
我感到越来越不爽
I felt more and more uncomfortable.
那种感觉是那么的特别
It was something quite special,\nthat feeling.
一种残酷的 可拍的压抑
An oppressive, hideous constraint,...
就像坐在刚刚杀死的人的鬼魂旁边
..as if I were sitting with the small ghost\nof somebody I had just killed.
耶稣基督
Jesus!
什么？
What?
我们能在加油站边停一停吗？
Can we stop at a gas station?
只要你愿意 去哪儿都行
We can go anywhere you like.
那么好吧 我需要去加油站
Well, I need a gas station.
我里面伤到了
I hurt inside.
那么 你想要什么？
Well, what do you expect?
我是个黄花大闺女 看看你都对我做了什么
I was a daisy-fresh girl,\nand look what you've done to me.
我大可以打电话给警察告诉他们你强奸了我 \n你个肮脏的老男人
I should call the police and tell them\nthat you raped me, you dirty old man.
-麻烦你帮我洗一下挡风玻璃\n-好的 先生
-Just wash the windscreen, would you?\n-Yes, sir.
拿了点饼干
Got some cookies.
我想给在医院的老妈打个电话 号码是多少？
I want to call Mother in hospital.\nWhat's the number?
进来 你没法打给她
Get in. You can't call the hospital.
为什么不？
Why not?
进来吧
Just get in the car.
把门关好
Slam the door.
为什么我不能想给我老妈打电话？如果我想打呢？
Why can't I call my own mother\nif I want to?
因为你妈妈已经去世了
Because your mother's dead.
嘘 嘘
Shh... Shh...
我们那晚做得很温柔
We made up very gently that night.
你看 她没有别的地方可去
You see, she had nowhere else to go.
也就是那个时候我们开始了我们的长长的旅行
It was then that we began\nour extensive travels...
穿越了整个美国
..all over the United States.
♪ Now the native population\nand civilization is fine ♪
♪ That civilization\nis the thing for me to see ♪
♪ Whoa, bongo, bongo, bongo ♪
♪ I don't wanna leave the Congo,\nno, no, no, no, no, no ♪
-什么时候是最合适的买鸟的时间？\n-我不知道 什么时候是？
-When's the best time to buy a bird?\n-I don't know. When's the best time?
-当“降价”的时候
When it's going "cheep!"
别说我从来什么都没有给你
Don't say I never gave you anything.
喔！呀咩跌！我正在开车！
Ow! Don't! I'm trying to drive!
别搞 喔 不会吧！
Don't do that! Oh, no!
如果那些东西掉出去 我可不会停车
If it goes out the window, I won't stop.
别搞！这是什么？发卡？
Don't! What are these? Hair grips?
♪ Civilisation ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ I'll stay right here ♪
看！他们有魔力手指
Look! They have Magic Fingers.
好
Good.
我要去洗个澡
I need to shower.
给我一个25美分硬币和10美分硬币
Give me a quarter and a dime.
干吗？
What for?
用魔力手指
For the Magic Fingers.
我的魔力手指还不够用？
My magic fingers aren't enough?
♪ Amor-r-r, amor-r-r, amor-r-r-r-r ♪
♪ This w-word s-so s-sweet that I r-repeat ♪
♪ Means I adore you-u-u-u-u ♪
♪ Amor-r-r-r-r, amor-r-r-r-r, amor-r-r-r-r... ♪
一起洗澡很不错 洛！
Good shower for once, Lo!
水温控制的一级棒
First-rate temperature control!
嗷！啊！
Ow! Argh!
-啊！洛！\n-嗯？
-Agh! Lo!\n-Hmm?
老天爷 洛！我在这里洗澡的时候别冲马桶！
My God, Lo! Don't flush when I'm in here!
什么？
What is that?
什么是什么？
What's what?
你嘴里的那个东西
That thing in your mouth.
是个嘴嚼子
It's a jawbreaker.
它可以弄烂你的嘴\n想要不？
It's supposed to break your jaw.\nWant one?
给我 我受够了那个噪音
Just give it to me.\nI've had it with that noise.
-快点 吐出来 搞得我头疼死了\n-这东西很好玩
-Come on, spit it out. I've got a headache.\n-It's good!
听着 快点给我 吐出来
Look, just give it to me, will you?\nSpit it out.
我看不到你你就是百分之百的好
You look a hundred per cent better\nwhen I can't see you.
我们选择了迂回的路线
We took a circuitous route -\nto put it mildly.
我们最终的目的地早被我抛到了脑后
In the back of my mind\nwas our eventual destination.
比尔兹利大学 是我最终开始我的教职的地方
Beardsley College, where I would finally\ntake up my teaching position.
但是目前对我来说 我需要继续前进 继续驾驶
But in the front of my mind was\nthe need to keep going, keep driving.
洛 这是我最后一次让你开这个车
Lo, that's the last time\nI let you drive this car.
在这个方框里面
Serve into this square.
而且 不管我们的争吵
And, despite our tiffs,...
打到界内 洛 试试看打倒界内
In the square, Lo.\nTry and get it in the square.
不管她造成的麻烦 危险以及所有的无助
..despite the fuss she made, and\nthe danger and hopelessness of it all,...
直到我的大脑
Aim for my head.
不管这一切 我简直是在天堂里
..despite all that, I was in paradise.
这个天堂的天空的颜色跟地狱之火一样
A paradise whose skies\nwere the color of hell flames,...
但它仍然是天堂
..but a paradise still.
我知道你已经接受了比尔兹利大学的教职
I know you have accepted a post\nat Beardsley College,...
而且我也知道 学业第一 学业最终而且学业永远重要
..and I know that there,\nacademics are first, last and always.
但是 那不是我们 希姆莱先生
Well, that's not us, Mr Himmler.
嗯 在比尔兹利预科学院
Uh... Here at Beardsley Prep,...
我们强调的是三个DS
..what we stress are the three Ds.
戏剧 舞会以及约会
Dramatics, dancing and dating.
现在 我知道教士在这一切背后监察 是吗？教士？
Now, I know that the Reverend Rigger is\nbehind us on this. Aren't you, Reverend?
-一直 普拉特女士 每个细节\n-那么你看 汉伯先生
-All the way, Miss Pratt. Every inch.\n-So you see, Mr Humper,...
在现在的青春期中 中世纪的约会不如周末的约会有活力
..for the modern preadolescent, medieval\ndates are less vital than weekend ones.
-什么？周末的什么？\n-约会 汉伯先生
-What? Weekend what?\n-Dates, Mr Humping.
哦 先生
Uh... boys.
♪ By myself alone at home ♪
♪ Feelin' blue ♪
我还没有对我现在的角色完全准备好
I was not quite prepared\nfor the reality of my dual role.
一方面 去侵蚀一个天真的 ?的欲念
On the one hand,\nthe willing corrupter of an innocent,...
另一方面 快乐的家庭主妇汉伯特
..and on the other,\nHumbert the happy housewife.
莱茵河在哪里？
Where's the river Rhine?
我不知道
I don't know.
你应该知道这些
You should know that.
-为什么？\n-那里有很多大的战斗
-Why?\n-Big battles there in the Great War.
塞纳河在哪里？
Where's the river Seine?
我不知道
I don't know.\nI don't know.
我想你应该学过这些
I thought you were supposed\nto have learnt these.
这对这些没兴趣
It's not what I'm on.
你们的这所学校看起来很放松
It seems to be pretty relaxed,\nthis school of yours.
♪ When I was a kid about half past three ♪
♪ My ma said\n"Daughter, come here to me" ♪
♪ Says "Things may come\nand things may go" ♪
♪ "But this is one thing\nyou ought to know" ♪
♪ "Oh, t'ain't what you do,\nit's the way that you do it" ♪
♪ "T'ain't what you do,\nit's the way that you do it" ♪
♪ "That's what... ♪
我想去演话剧
I'm supposed to be in a play.
-什么话剧？\n-我不知道
-What play?\n-I don't know.
某些话剧
Some play.
就在学校里
At school.
和一个从巴特勒学院的男生？
With the boys from Butler's Academy?
我不知道
I don't know.
或许吧
Maybe.
我不认为这是个好主意
I don't think it's a good idea.
你在剥夺我的公民权利
You're depriving me of my civil rights.
你从哪里学到的这些词语?
Where did you learn that language?
我很聪明
I'm intelligent.
如果我愿意 我有权参演话剧
I have a right to be in a play if I want.
我说不行就不行
Not if I say you don't.
你喜欢吗？
D'you like that?
你还想要更多 对吧？
You want more, don't you?
我也要有些东西
I want things, too.
什么？
What?\nWhat?
东西
Things.
你知道我一周的零花钱是一美元吧？
You know how my allowance\nis a dollar a week?
是的我知道
Yes, I know.
那么 我想应该是两美元
Well, I think it should be two dollars.
我说 我想应该是两美元
I said, I think it should be two dollars.
一块五
A dollar fifty.
我真的认为应该是两美元
I really do think it should be two dollars.
对不对？
Am I right?
老天爷 对
God, yes.
两美元
Two dollars.
而且我还要演话剧
And I get to be in the play.
噢 夜晚的玫瑰夫人
Oh, rosy mistress of the night.
你让如此多的猎手心情激荡
You have enchanted\nmany a hunter's heart.
但是这次 我的迷人的夫人
But this time, my temptress,...
你遇见了你的对手
..you have met your match.
比猎手强了太多
For far more than a hunter,...
我
..l...
是个诗人
..am a poet.
-夜幕已经垂下 罗德明哥
-The night has fallen, Rodrigo.\n-The...\n-
打住！打住！莫娜
Hold it! Hold it! Mona...
等一会 我要和多丽丝说两句话
Give us a moment.\nI'd like a word with Dolores.
当你说“欢笑的魔力”的时候 对这些猎手使用魔力
When you say "your larking charms",\nuse your charms for the hunter.
因为是你巫婆
Because you're the witch.
你要把这些猎手带往你的巢穴
You're bringing the hunter to your lair.
-嗨 汉伯特先生\n-你好 莫娜
-Hi, Mr Humbert.\n-Hello, Mona.
话剧 对吗？
Some play, huh?
你是女神 用你女神的魔力
You're nymphs.\nUse your nymph's charms.
引诱这些猎手
Seduce the hunter.
看 看到那边的那个人了吗？
Look. See right there?
他是真正的剧作家 克莱尔·奎尔第\n你能相信吗？
That's the actual playwright, Clare Quilty.\nCan you believe it?
用音乐让你变形
Let the music transform you.
你感到你已经变成了巫婆
You'll feel that you've become a witch.
-你是个巫婆
-You're a witch!
-这出戏剧很不错 莫娜？\n-是的 非常政治化
-This play any good, Mona?\n-Yeah. It's very political.
巫婆！巫婆！
Witch! Witch!
风大点 风大点
More wind! More wind!
你是巫婆
You're a witch!
不是吗？
Aren't you?
风大点 我需要风大点
More wind! I need more wind!
她是巫婆！她正在跳舞！
The witches now! The witches' dance!
在风中跳舞！
In the wind!
她对我的求欢表现的越来越冷淡
As she grew cooler\ntowards my advances,...
我逐渐习惯给她买她想要的东西
..l became accustomed\nto purchasing her favors.
我从来不知道她把钱藏在哪里
Where she hid the money, I never knew.
停下来
Stop it!
我相信她正在攒钱好让她能够在经济上摆脱我
I was convinced she was storing it away\nin order to finance her escape from me.
你怎么能在做到一半的时候涨价！
You can't expect me to pay extra\nin the middle!
嗷！啊！
Ow! Argh!
她是个可爱的孩子 海兹先生
She's a lovely child, Mr Haze,...
但是她的初步性成熟好像给她带来了麻烦
..but the onset of sexual maturing\nseems to be giving her trouble.
-这是你的观察 是吗？神父?\n-是的 普拉特女士
-Isn't that your observation, Reverend?\n-To the tee, Miss Pratt.
-那么 你看 这是对一个14岁大的多丽丝的大致印象
So, you see, it is the general impression\nthat 14-year-old Dolores...
她病态地对性事缺乏兴趣
..is morbidly disinterested\nin sexual matters.
她有没有跟你说过这些事？
Does she never speak\nabout these... matters?
那么
Well...
那就是了
That's just it.
什么？
What's just it?
那 就是了
That's... just it.
她从没说过一句话
She hasn't said anything.
她从没说过一个词
She hasn't breathed a word.
嗯 但是谁能说呢？
Uh... But who has?
你 你是在说我
Are... Are you saying that I've...
没错
Exactly.
这是个非常严重的事
This is a very serious matter.
我们试着告诉你
What we're trying to say to you...
作为家庭的一员
..is that someone in the family,...
或许你?
..maybe you,...
对我来说难以启齿
This is very difficult for me.
好吧 这么说吧
Well, let me put it this way.
你们家庭的一员应该教导这个可爱的孩子 ?
Someone in the family\nought to instruct that dear child...
人类繁衍的流程
..in the process of human reproduction.
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
-抱歉\n-我知道这让你很尴尬
-I'm so sorry.\n-I see that I've embarrassed you.
你作为一个父亲应该把这些事情都做好
Yet you, as her father,\nought to take the matter well in hand.
是的 不用但系 普拉特女士
Yes. Worry not, Miss Pratt.
我 嗯 我知道 我会搞好的
I... um... I have... this matter in hand.
那么 好吧
Oh, well,...
这就是我要说的
..that's all I need to say.
请讲
Yes?
哦 是吗？
Oh, yes?
她没去？
She missed?
哦
Oh.
再见
Bye.
钢琴课怎么样？
How are the piano lessons going?
很好
Fine.
很好 很帮 很精彩
Great. Excellent. Wonderful.
牛逼 完美
Terrif. Perfect.
特别是你前两次课都没去
Especially since you missed the last two.
你去哪儿了？
Where were you?
我去哪儿了？
Where was l?
我告诉过你吧
I should have told you before.
我去公园了 和莫娜在排练话剧
I was in the park.\nI was rehearsing the play with Mona.
这是你的借口
That's your story?
我是在干这些
That's what I was doing.
好吧 把莫娜的电话号码给我
OK. Give me Mona's phone number.
-莫娜的电话？\n-把莫娜的电话号码给我
-Mona's phone number?\n-Just give me Mona's phone number.
克劳森 57241
Klausen 57241.
请问莫娜在吗？
Is Mona there, please?
-莫娜 这是多丽丝的父亲\n-哦 你好 先生
-Mona, this is Dolores's father.\n-Oh, hello, sir.
莫娜 你和多丽丝
Mona, were you and Dolores...
过去两个星期二下午去公园排练了？
..rehearsing the play in the park\nfor the past two Tuesday afternoons?
嗯 让我想想
Um... Let's see.
前两个周二？
The last two Tuesdays?
其中一个是在昨天 莫娜
One of them, Mona, was yesterday.
是的 先生 没错
You know, sir, that's... absolutely right.
实在是抱歉
I feel awfully bad about it.
我是那个唯一该责备的人 先生
I alone am to blame, sir.
在公园里排练是我的主意
The whole rehearsing in the park thing\nwas my idea.
我们这么做是因为我们不想让你担心
We did it cos we didn't want\nto get on your nerves.
满意了？
Well?
她确认了？
Did she confirm?
是的
She did.
而且我一点也不怀疑是你让她这么说的
And I've no doubt\nshe'd been well instructed by you.
实际上 我一点也不怀疑你把我们之间的一切告诉了她
In fact, I've no doubt\nyou've told her all about us.
听着 洛 这一切必须停止
Look, Lo, this has got to stop.
我不知道你想干吗 但不管是什么
I don't know what you're up to,\nbut whatever it is,...
我要把你从比尔兹利送出去越快越好 除非这一切停止
..I'll yank you out of Beardsley as fast as\nI can pack a suitcase unless this stops!
除非什么停止？
Unless what stops?
-你知道！\n-慢点 先生！
-You know what!\n-Take it easy, mister!
-把你的钱都给我\n-离我远点 你个变态！
-Show me every penny...\n-Leave me alone, you pervert!
-你要离开我 知道\n-没错 任何一个人都不想和你待在一起
-You're running away from me, I know.\n-Yes, I am! Anyone'd run away from you!
-把你藏起来的钱给我！\n-那钱是我挣来的！
-Show me what you hid!\n-I earned that money!
好吧 杀了我吧 就跟你谋杀我妈妈一样
Go ahead, murder me.\nLike you murdered my mother.
对不起
I'm sorry.
就跟你谋杀了我妈妈一样杀了我吧！
Murder me like you murdered my mother!
闭嘴 闭嘴！
Shut up. Shut up!
就跟你谋杀了我妈妈一样杀了我吧！
Murder me like you murdered my mother!
-停下来！\n-来吧 杀了我吧
-Stop that!\n-Go ahead! Murder me!
来吧 杀了我吧！我让你杀了我！
Go on, murder me!\nI'm asking you to murder me!
-住嘴！\n-杀了我吧！杀了我吧！
-Shut up!\n-Murder me! Murder me!
-多丽丝 闭嘴！\n-我恨你 我恨你！
-Dolores, shut up!\n-I hate you! I hate you!
安静
Calm down.
-安静
-Calm down!
-回来 洛
-Come back, Lo!
-凶手！
Murderer!
抱歉 抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起 对不起！对不起！
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
真不知道你们这些人以为你们是什么 又哭又叫的！
I do not know who you people think\nyou are, screaming and carrying on!
我女儿的朋友 抱歉 我要走了
My daughter's friend.\nI'm sorry. I really can't stay.
很好 我刚才试着往家里打电话
Oh, good. I was just trying\nto reach you at home.
-我已经做了决定\n-你做了决定？
-I've come to a decision.\n-You have?
是的
Yeah.
给我买杯喝的
So buy me a drink.
你想喝什么？
What would you like?
嗯 我想要 嗯 冰激凌苏打水
Um... I'd like, uh, ice-cream soda...
还要另外加巧克力酱
..with extra chocolate syrup.
请
Please.
我什么都不要 谢谢
Nothing for me, thanks.
洛
Lo...
告诉我你的决定
So tell me.
急什么？
What's the rush?
给她钱 我们忘记这次不快
Pay her and let's blow this joint.
你知道她说了什么 ?
And do you know what she said,...
这个抛弃我 嘲弄我
..this girl who had been spurning me,\nmocking me,...
一个小时之前曾密谋离开我的女孩子
..plotting her escape from me\nonly hours before?
说她想马上离开比尔兹利
She said she wanted\nto leave Beardsley then and there.
她想开始另外一场旅行
She wanted to take another trip,...
只是这次她将选择我们去哪里
..only this time she would choose\nwhere we would go.
-好吗？我选择？OK？\n-好
-OK? I choose? OK?\n-Yes.
汉伯特先生赞成吗？
Did Humbert hum his assent?
哦 是的
Oh, yes.
我感激地封上了自己的命运
I sealed my fate gratefully.
洛丽塔
Lolita.
抱我上床
Take me to bed.
找烟头
Look out for cigarette hangover.
嗨 我是克莱尔·奎尔第
Hi. I'm Clare Quilty.
记住 有超过一百万吸烟者
Remember, over a million smokers...
我们现在应该是在
So we have to be in...
威斯呆一周
..Wace in exactly one week.
为什么在威斯呆一周？
But why Wace in a week?
因为我们应该看看那些神奇舞会开始时的庆祝舞蹈
Cos we gotta see the... ceremonial dances\nwhen they open the Magic Caves.
另外 准确的两周 另外4天之后
And... exactly two weeks\nand four days later,...
我们应该到达埃尔芬斯顿 看到了吗？
..we have to arrive in Elphinstone. See?
是的
Yes.
我们在那里爬红石山
That's where we climb the Red Rock.
我们应该准准确确地两周零四天之后爬这座山？
We have to climb this rock\nexactly two weeks and four days later?
没错
Exactly.
噢 我真是太兴奋了
Oh, I'm so excited.
我没法告诉你我哪天确定我们被跟踪的
I cannot tell you the exact day I first knew\nfor certain that we were being followed.
洛 打开手套柜拿一支笔一个笔记本
Lo, reach into the glove compartment\nand get the pad and pencil.
好了吗？现在开始写
Got it? Now write this down.
Connecticut.
怎么拼？
How do you spell that?
C-O-N-N.
是吗？
Is that it?
不是 现在写下来
No. Now write down...
..PJ...
..44...
..396.
好了 给我
All right, give it to me.
好的
All right.
放进手套柜里 别吧口香糖弄到上面 会搞的
Put it in the glove box.\nDon't put gum on it cos it'll get...
你怎么把口香糖搞得到处都是？
Why have you got your gum everywhere?
把那个东西放进手套柜
Put that in the glove box.
后面有个警探跟着咱们
There's a detective following us.
他看起来很像我的叔叔古斯塔夫
He looks rather like my Uncle Gustave.
他很聪明 我们的追踪者
He was clever, our pursuer.
他一直在改变车子
He kept changing cars.
但是他的相貌对我来说真实得跟
But his presence was as real to me...
我自己的呼吸一样
..as my own breath.
后来他就突然不再出现了 我想知道他是不是已经知道了这一切
Then suddenly he would disappear\nand I'd wonder if i'd imagined everything.
洛！那个男人跟你说了什么？
Lo! What did that man say to you?
♪ Bags around your eyeballs\nwhich is red instead of white ♪
-他跟你说什么了？\n-那个跟我说话的男人？
-What did he say to you?\n-The guy I was talking to?
-是的 听着
-Yeah. Look...\n-♪ Shucks, I shoulda known... ♪
快点告诉我他跟你说什么了
Just tell me what he said to you.
他问我有没有地图 他一定是把他的弄丢了
He asked me if I had a map.\nHe must've been lost.
♪ My heart's plumb gone ♪
♪ Cos you used temptation ♪
♪ It'd be thrilling... if'n you're willing ♪
听着 我已经告诉过你跟陌生人谈话的害处你完全不知道
Look, I've told you about\ntalking to strangers. You've no idea...
洛 听我说
Lo, listen to me.
你很年轻 别人会占你便宜的
You're very young\nand people can take advantage of you.
难以想象
Very hard to imagine.
那个跟踪我们的男人是个条子
That man was the cop\nwho's been following us.
你必须告诉我他跟你说的每一个字
You have to tell me\nexactly what you told him.
如果他真是个条子 最糟糕的事就是让他知道我们吓坏了
If he really is a cop, the worst thing\nwe can do is let him know we're scared.
然后他就知道我们有罪
Then he'll know that we're guilty.
或者 你有罪
Or rather, that you're guilty.
♪ Don't sit under the apple tree\nwith anyone else but me... ♪
♪ With anyone else but me ♪
♪ With anyone else but me, no, no, no ♪
♪ Anyone else but you ♪
♪ No, no, don't go under the apple tree ♪
方向盘有点问题
There's something wrong\nwith the steering.
哦 哇
Oh, whoa!
哦！小心！
Ow! Watch it!
你在搞么比？
What are you doing?!
你车胎爆了 先生
You got a flat, mister.
♪ Open the door, and let me in ♪
♪ Richard, why don't you open the door? ♪
嘿
Hey...
嘿！
Hey!
嘿 你！回来！
Hey, you! Come back here!
洛！
Lo!
洛！洛！
Lo! Lo!
洛！
Lo!
快点拉手闸
Put on the handbrake!
快点把手闸拉上！洛！
Pull the handbrake up! Lo!
洛！把手闸拉上 把车停下
Lo! Pull on the handbrake. Stop the car.
把手闸拉上 停下来 快点拉
Put the handbrake on. Down there! Pull it!
-喔
-Ow!
耶稣基督啊
Jesus Christ!
你以为你在干吗？
What did you think you were doing?
你应该感谢我
You should thank me.
车子跑了但是我停住了它
The car was rolling and I stopped it.
你应该感谢我
You should thank me.
把手套柜里的笔记本给我
Pass me the pad\nin the glove compartment.
我们吧他的车牌号码写下来真是太聪明了
It was smart of us\nto write his number down.
什么？
What...?
你干什么了？
What have you...
洛
Lo...
洛 对不起
Lo, I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry!
回来 回来
Come here. Come here.
滚开！
Get away!
洛
Lo...
对不起 对不起 对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
要不要去镇子上给你买点水果？
Shall I walk down to the town\nand get you some fruit?
香蕉
Bananas.
只要香蕉？
Just bananas?
只要香蕉
Just bananas.
♪ Open the door, Richard ♪
♪ Open the door and let me in ♪
♪ Richard … Why don't you open that door? ♪
♪ Borrow confidently from HFC ♪
奎尔第今晚可以来我们演播室 因为他现在在德克萨斯 威斯
Quilty can't be here in our studio\nbecause he's in Wace, Texas tonight...
正在写他的最新话剧的第一章
..working on the premiere\nof his brand-new play.
但是我想欢迎他的写作伙伴
But I want to welcome\nhis writing partner,...
可爱的充满天分的 小姐
..the lovely and talented\nMiss Vivian Darkbloom.
让我们给她一个热情的德克萨斯式欢迎
Let's give her a warm Texas welcome.
你出去了
You've been out.
我刚刚起床
I just got up.
别骗我
Don't lie to me.
好吧 我出去了一小会
Well, I did go out for a second.
你出去了这么久 我想看看你是不是回来了
You were gone so long.\nI wanted to see if you were coming back.
你告诉我他是谁？他是谁？
You tell me who it is! Who is it?
他是谁？告诉我他是谁？
Who is it? Tell me who it is.
告诉我 他是谁？
You tell me. Who is it?
谁？
Who...?
-告诉我
-Tell me.
求求你 告诉我
Please, tell me.
求求你告诉我
Please tell me.
求求你！
Please!
求求你 告诉我！
Please... tell... me!
求求你！求求你！
Please... please...
求求你！
Please...
告诉我！
..tell me!
求求你
Please...
..please...
求求你
我带你们去29号房间
I'll show you to room number 29.
这是我们最好的房间
It's one of our nicer rooms.
你女儿怎么了？ 她病了吗？
Say, what's wrong\nwith your little daughter? Is she ill?
哦 不 她只是有点
Oh, no. She's just feeling a bit... um...
老天爷 洛！
My God, Lo!
你怎么样？
Are you all right?
我觉得 我觉得不舒服
I don't feel... I don't feel very well.
是病毒
It's a virus.
并不严重 这两周有40个这样的病人
Nothing serious.\nI've had 40 cases in two weeks.
-我可以带她回家吗？\n-我们必须让她在医院观察一夜
-So can I take her home?\n-We're gonna keep her here overnight.
让她多喝水 帮助她睡眠
Keep her hydrated, help her sleep.
你怎么不去睡觉？你呆在这也没用
Why don't you get some sleep?\nIt won't help if you catch it.
我已经睡过了 我很担心
I think I have already.\nI feel dreadful.
-或许我应该留下来\n-回去吧
-Maybe I should stay.\n-Go.
明天早上给我打电话
Call us in the morning.
-把花给我吧\n-谢谢
-Here, I'll take those.\n-Thank you.
嗯 是的 你好 我是汉伯特先生
Uh, yes, hello. This is Mr Humbert.
我打电话来问问我女儿怎么样了 多丽丝·海兹
I'm calling to see how my... daughter,\nDolores Haze, is.
哦 她好多了
Oh, she's much better.
她很早就起来了 烧也退了
She was up early. No trace of fever.
她叔叔古斯塔夫来接她走 我们签字让她离开了
And when Uncle Gustave came for her,\nwe signed her out.
谁？ 谁？
Who? Wh... Wh... Who?
古斯塔夫叔叔 多丽丝这么叫他
Uncle Gustave, Dolores called him.
他有一只聪明伶俐的狗 他真是个大好人 笑容可掬的
He had a sweet little dog.\nHe was the nicest man. Had a big smile.
等等
Wait, Ted.
-你就让她跟他走了？\n-哦 是的 他用现金付的药费
-And you let her go with him?\n-Oh, yes. He paid the bill in cash.
他们说让你不用担心 他们会在爷爷家等你
They said to tell you not to worry,\nand they'll be at Grandpa's expecting you.
-然后他们进了那辆漂亮的凯迪拉克
-Then they went off in that nice Cadillac.
喂？
Hello?
嘿！
Hey!
护士
Nurse!
-她在哪儿？\n-谁？
-Where is she?\n-Who?
谁把她带走了？有人把我女儿带走了
Who took her?\nSomebody took my daughter.
-你应该跟一生说\n-但是谁把她带走了？
-You need to talk to the doctor.\n-But who took her?
我女儿昨天晚上还在这儿
My daughter was in there last night.
-谁把她带走了？\n-嘿 放松 老兄
-Who took her away?\n-Hey, relax, pal!
别告诉我让我放松！我在找我女儿！医生！
Don't tell me to relax!\nI'm looking for my daughter! Doctor!
医生！医生！
Doctor! Doctor!
你对她做了什么？
What have you done with her?
她在哪儿?她在哪儿?
Where is she? Where is she?
告诉我她在哪儿！她在哪儿?
Tell me where she is! Where is she?
她去哪儿了？哪儿？哪儿？哪儿？
Where has she gone?\nWhere? Where? Where?
滚开 混蛋！
You leave me alone, you bastards!
你个该死的恶魔
You fucking fiends!
告诉我她在哪儿！
Tell me where she is!
帮我搞定那个人！
Get me to that man!
我只是在找我的女儿！
I'm just looking for my daughter!
-我说过放松！\n-我只想知道她在哪儿
-I said relax!\n-I want to know where she -
对不起 对不起 对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起
Sorry.
对不起 我只是有点
I'm sorry. I'm just a little bit...
我想我只是有点 ?喝多了 对不起
I think I may just have...\nhad a little too much to drink. Sorry.
我很担心我女儿 你知道
I'm very worried\nabout my daughter, you see.
但是她跟古斯塔夫叔叔在一起
But she's with her Uncle Gustave.
她应该没事
So she'll be all right.
非常抱歉 请原谅我
I'm very sorry. Please forgive me.
她去她爷爷的农场了
She's gone to her... grandpa's farm.
她肯定没事
She'll be absolutely fine there.
哪里有比那更好的地方？
What better place for her?
我 我很好
I'm... I'm fine.
对不起
Please, I'm sorry.
对不起 非常感谢
So sorry. Thank you very much.
对不起 对不起
Sorry... Sorry.
非常抱歉
So sorry.
我找了所有我们去过的地方
I searched all our old haunts...
好几个月 那些痕迹依然温暖
..and for several months\nthe trail remained warm.
那个贼 绑架犯 无论你叫他什么
The thief, the kidnapper,\nwhatever you want to call him,...
他很聪明
..he was clever.
他肯定用的是假名
He would disguise his name.
但是我一直认识他的字迹
But I could always tell his handwriting.
嗯 先生！
Um... Sir!
他写的Ts, Ws, LS非常特别
He had very peculiar Ts, Ws and Ls.
你知道他的名字吗？
Do you know his name?
他看起来什么样？
What does he look like?
-让我帮你\n-不 请你
-Let me help.\n-No, please...
女士 抱歉 我正在找 ?
Ladies, I'm sorry. We're trying to find...
我想你们肯定很难理解
It must be hard\nfor you who already know who it was...
我的神经质
..to understand my mystification.
或者你们可能认为我有幻想症
Or maybe you think\nI was imagining things.
我女儿
..my daughter.
或许你们认为不可能有另外一个像我这样的人
Maybe you think it impossible that\nthere could have been another like me.
另外一个喜欢早熟少女的男人跟踪了我们整个丑陋的平原
Another mad lover of nymphets following\nus over the great and ugly plains.
那么 你是对的 当然
Well, you are right, of course.
没有一个人会像我一样
There was no-one else like me.
最终这些线索逐渐消失
Eventually the trail went cold and dead.
我最后回到了冰冷的 死气沉沉的比尔兹利
And I went back to cold, dead Beardsley.
“亲爱的爸爸 一切还好吗？”
"Dear Dad, how's everything?"
“我结婚了 我马上就要生孩子了”
"I'm married. I'm going to have a baby."
“我想应该是圣诞节前后”
"I guess it'll come\nright around Christmas."
“写这封信对我来说很艰难”
"This is a hard letter to write."
“我们很困难 因为我们没有足够的
"I'm going nuts\nbecause we don't have enough...
来付账单并离开这里“
..to pay our debts and get out of here."
“迪克许诺会在阿拉斯加找个好工作”
"Dick has been promised\na big job in Alaska."
“你仍然对我很生气吗？”
"Are you still mad at me?"\n"Are you still mad at me?"
“请寄给我一张支票 我想三四百块钱就足够了 ”
"Please send us a cheque, Dad. We could\nmanage with three or four hundred,...
更少也可以 任何帮助都可以“
..or even less. Anything is welcome."
我已经受够了悲哀和困苦
"I have gone through\nmuch sadness and hardship."
“期待你的回复 多丽”
"Yours expecting, Dolly."
“理查德·F太太”
"Mrs Richard F...
“席勒”
..Schiller."
嗯
Well!
请进
Come in.
你 莫利 呆在外面
You, Molly, stay out.
好女孩
Good girl.
老公在家？
Husband at home?
嗯
Yeah.
你想坐哪儿？摇椅还是沙发？
Where do you wanna sit?\nThe rocker or the divan?
过来跟我一起坐在沙发上吧
Come sit with me on the divan.
就是他？
Is that him?
梯子上的那个？
Up the ladder?
你想让我叫他进来吗？
You want me to call him in?
不用了
No.
他不是我找的那个人
He's not the one I want.
他不是什么?
He's not the what?
你知道我指的是什么
You know what I mean.
他在哪儿？
Where is he?
听着
Look...
迪克跟整件事没有关系 他以为你是我父亲
Dick has nothing to do with all that stuff.\nHe thinks you're my father.
请不要把事情搞那么复杂
Please don't bring up all that muck.
-好吧 我自己会搞清楚\n-你真不知道？
-All right, I'll find out myself.\n-You really don't know?
老天爷 爸爸 是奎尔第
My God, Dad, it was Quilty.
是克莱尔·奎尔第
It was Clare Quilty.
对
Yes.
是的 当然是他
Yes, of course.
奎尔第
Quilty.
是的
Yeah.\nYeah.
他是唯一的一个让我疯狂的男人
He was the only man\nI was ever really crazy about.
那我呢？
What about me?
他带你去哪儿了？
Where did he take you?
快点告诉我
Just tell me.
好吧 每个人都知道他喜欢小姑娘
Well, everybody knew he liked little girls.
他曾经在他在帕金顿的豪宅里把她们拍下来
He used to film them in his mansion\nover in Parkington, Pavor Manor.
但是我没有干那些事情
But I wasn't gonna do all those things.
什么事？
All what things?
两个男孩两个女孩或者
Two girls and two boys or...
我不清楚 大概三四个男人
..l don't know, three or four men.
另外 Vivian把整个过程拍下来
And Vivian was filming the whole thing.
我说“不 我才不会给这些禽兽男人们吹箫”
I said "No, I'm not gonna blow\nall those beastly boys."
“我想跟你”
"I want you."
所以她把我除外了
So he threw me out.
我看着她 看了又看
I looked and looked at her...
我知道 就像我知道我必死无疑那样清楚
..and I knew,\nas clearly as I know that I will die,...
我是如此的爱她 胜过我所看到的所能想象到的地球上的任何事物
..that I loved her more than anything\nI'd ever seen or imagined on earth.
她以前是一个妖女 现在却像一片枯叶
She was only the dead leaf echo\nof the nymphet from long ago...
但是我爱她 这个洛丽塔
..but I loved her, this Lolita,...
苍白、臃肿、混俗 怀着别的男人的孩子
..pale and polluted\nand big with another man's child.
她可以褪色 可以枯萎 我不在乎
She could fade and wither -I didn't care.
但我只要看她一眼
I would still go mad with tenderness...
万般柔情 涌上心头
..at the mere sight other face.
洛丽塔
Lolita...
从这里到那个你熟悉的汽车
From here to that old car\nthat you know so well...
只有25步的距离
..is a stretch of 25 paces.
走过这25步
Make those 25 steps...
跟我在一起吧
..with me, now.
你是说如果我跟你一起去汽车旅馆你就会给我点钱？
You're saying you'll give us some money\nif I go to a motel with you?
不是 不是！！
No... No!
我是说你离开这里和我一起生活 一起死去 和我一起干任何事
I'm saying leave here and come live\nwith me, die with me, everything with me.
你简直是疯了
You're crazy.
如果你拒绝你仍然能拿到这些钱
If you refuse, you still get the money.
-真的？\n-是的
-Really?\n-Yeah.
拿着 拿着吧
There. Have it.
哦 老天爷
Oh my God.
你给了我四千美元？
You're giving us four thousand bucks?
-谢谢\n-不要
-Thank you...\n-No...
不要碰我
Don't touch me.
你一碰我我就会死
I'll die if you touch me.
我只想告诉你\n你有机会跟我一起走
Just tell me...\nthere's a chance you'll come with me.
不 亲爱的
No, honey.
我宁愿跟克莱尔走
I'd almost rather go back with Clare.
噢
Oh...
好了 我走了
I'll go now.
-我让迪克回来跟你告别？\n-不用了 我根本不想见他
-Can I call Dick in to say goodbye?\n-No. I don't want to see him, at all.
我只想走
I just want to go.
洛 你能不能忘记我对你做过的事情？
Lo, can you ever forget\nwhat I've done to you?
说再见 莫利
Say goodbye, Molly.
跟爸爸说再见
Say goodbye to my dad.
迪克！你猜有什么好消息！
Dick! Guess what!
陪审团的先生女士们
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,...
我必须说我对在煤山那次告别以前所作的事感到后悔
..l have to say that I regret all I did\nbefore that last goodbye in Coalmont.
但我从来不对后来发生的事后悔
But I regret nothing of what came after.
哦 你是谁？
Now, who are you?
你是 是不是布鲁斯特？
Are you, by any chance, Brewster?
你知道不 你看起来不像杰克 布鲁斯特
You know, you don't look\nlike Jack Brewster.
我是说 神似并不让人感到意外
I mean, the resemblance\nis not particularly striking.
有人说他有个兄弟有一个同样的电话公司
Somebody told me he had a brother\nwith the same phone company.
我不是什么布鲁斯特兄弟
I'm neither of the Brewsters.
到路边停下
Pull over!
你记不记得有个小女孩名字叫
Do you recall a little girl named...
多丽丝·海兹？
..Dolores Haze?
你晓得不 我是她父亲
You see, I'm her father.
瞎扯
Nonsense.
你是外国人 你是外国势力的特工
You're a foreigner.\nYou're an agent of a foreign power.
你是个外国文化特工
You're a foreign literary agent.
她是我女儿
She was my daughter.
她是我孩子
She was my child.
哦 你知道 我喜欢孩子们
Oh, you know, I adore children myself.
也喜欢他们的父亲
And fathers...
我喜欢父亲
I love fathers.
啊
Ah...
坐下！
Sit down!
哦 找到了
Oh. There they are.
现在我需要一些火柴 借个火？
Now we need matches. You got a light?
奎尔第 你给我集中精神
Quilty, I want you to concentrate.
你马上就要死
You're about to die.
喔
Ooh.
耶稣
Jesus!
你想站着死还是坐着死？
Do you want to be executed\nstanding up or sitting down?
让我想想 让我想想 这是个很难回答的问题
Just let me think, let me think.\nIt's not an easy question.
我只想知道发生了什么事
Try to understand what is happening.
我 我 我我
I-l-l-l...
-记得多丽丝·海兹？\n-我愿意
-Remember Dolores Haze.\n-I'm willing...
我愿意试试 我 只是
I'm willing to try. I am. Just...
好吧 听着
OK. Listen.
我犯了个错误 我很后悔
I made a mistake, which I regret,...
真的
..sincerely.
我跟多丽之间什么都没发生 实际上 我性无能
I couldn't have any fun with your Dolly.\nI'm practically impotent is the sad truth.
但是她有个很棒的假期 见到了很多不错的人 嘿 你知道吧-
But she had a swell vacation, met some\nremarkable people. Hey, do you know -
站好别动！
Stay still!
噢 老天爷
Oh, God...
你骗了我
You cheated me.
你欺骗了我的救赎
You cheated me of my redemption.
-你必须得死\n-我不知道你在说什么
-You have to die.\n-I don't know what you're talking about.
我的大脑和舌头今天有点不听使唤
My memory and my eloquence\nare not at their best today.
但是真的 你必须承认你从来不是一个理想的继父
But really, you have to admit\nyou were never an ideal stepfather.
嗯？
Hm?
我没有强迫你的女儿加入我们
I did not force your protégée to join me.
是她让我把她带到一个快乐的家中
It was she who made me\nremove her to a happier home.
看看你四周 看到了吗？
Look around you. See?
你看到这座房子了？
You see this house?
夏天很凉快 很舒服 我建议你搬进来 嗯？
It's very cool in the summer. Comfortable.\nI suggest that you move in, hm?
我想你住在这里一定很开心
I think you'll be happy here.
你可以用我的衣柜
You can use my wardrobe.
我们有最可信赖的的女佣
We have the most reliable\nand bribable charwoman.
“清洁女工” 是一个美国式条款
"Cleaning lady" is the American term.
她不仅有女儿 还有孙女
She has not only daughters,\nshe has granddaughters.
我还知道一两个关于警察局长的事
And I know a thing or two\nabout the chief of police...
让他成为我的奴隶的事
..that makes him my slave.
我的奴隶 把枪扔掉
My slave. Drop the gun.
还有件事 把枪扔掉
And here's another thing. Drop the gun.
就在楼上 我还有独一无二的色情刊物的收藏品
I have, upstairs,\nthe most unique collection of erotica.
把枪扔掉 把枪扔掉
Drop the gun. Drop the gun.
另外 我还可以安排你去参加死刑执行
Also, moreover, I can arrange\nfor you to attend executions.
并不是每个人知道电椅是漆成黄色的
Not everybody knows\nthe chair is painted yellow.
来人救命啊
Somebody help!
啊！！
Aargh! Agh!
很疼 先生
That hurts, sir.
我亲爱的老兄 那很的很疼
That hurts atrociously, my dear fellow.
老天爷
God...
你真的不该一直穿成这个样子
You should not continue\nin this fashion, really.
滚出去！
Get out!
从这里滚出去！
Get out of here!
我听到了孩子们的欢声笑语
What I heard then was\nthe melody of children at play.
除此之外 没有别的
Nothing but that.
让我心灰意冷的并不是
And I knew that\nthe hopelessly poignant thing...
洛丽塔不在我身边
..was not Lolita's absence from my side...
而是这里的欢笑声中没有她
..but the absence other voice\nfrom that chorus.